Jhal
Hello Hello Friends Health Insurance This is
like a do, Mash Mitra Mandal welcomes you,
thank you very much for watching this video.
Today's topic
in health insurance is what is called shooting oneself in the foot.
See, on 31st March the
financial year has ended and today we are
starting Navratri, so I will tell you guys,
not in the last year, but in the last five years,
we started doing a very
strange thing,
someone started doing this again and again, now it seems to me that
inside the tiger,
this thing has happened in the policy on appointment,
Pet Naira, the person is such that he has a
policy, that
person has appointed some
insurance, friends,
now when I told him, then
within some time he told me that
if you do so much
then you will not have a policy, so
normally
all this happens
that he gets the information about the policy
and after 2 years I do not know
because of this,
now what type of things do they do normally, the people who are
Pradhan's people  Those who
buy policies from them have a very
common problem, I
always advise normal people,
I also reply on the same principle to myself, along with name and
fame, as per the policy selling, you should
not do any work with your eyes, let alone smoke, because you
cannot talk to anyone,
and Aishwarya in Bhai Saheb's chamber,
then you cannot see the girl properly, that is,
you cannot even see the question, so
now what is the problem that when I
buy the policy, the company
asks me around 20 direct questions whether
I have this disease or not, apart from this, some
companies include these diseases
around 145 260 in it and
although it is asked less nowadays, but 5
to 10 15 years ago, it used to be very
descriptive, then there used to be proposal forms, now
when you are buying the policy, first of all, normally,
it is not going to tell you what all
things are
declared and the correct way to delete it,
here  But on what scale do you discuss
these things, don't even tell them, if
you have any health issues today, any life-threatening condition, it is compulsory for you to
tell them, whether it was
your screen system condition, it was a
pre-existing male nurse, or it was a
pre-existing disease, or you have developed symptoms of something, or you got a
medical
checkup done to find out any disease,
your doctor messaged all these things, if
someone had stomach ache and all these
things to attend to, the company lied to you, the thing is that the
company does not have to
tell everything,
but
I have chicken pox, call Rahu, sometimes
typhoid, there is a person who is
buying a policy, then the
person from whom he bought the
policy for his parents six-eight months
ago, the same person is the director of the company, online
portal, talking simply, so while
discussing the policy, he told that
my mother had angiography done in 2013-14, if there is any
problem in the chest, then get it checked.
Nothing came out, it was clean, so that
gentleman, that is, the insurance
company's call center, during its active days, you
called from any other number or an unknown number and
told him that Sir, when there is nothing in your skin, then why is there a
need to tell, then
he did not tell you, the policy can be passed
comfortably within two days
but you
should call, but in the dark, there is definitely a
problem because this
non-disclosure
approach in your health issue, tell me
two, tell me five, it is necessary to tell,
what happens if you do not tell, it is possible, it can be done easily,
but when you are taking a policy solution
online or offline, and you
take a declaration in it, there are 12 important
declarations that whatever things I have told you to the best
of my knowledge, my honesty,
I will tell you that the medical checkup is
written somewhere from another company, it gets it
accepted so that if tomorrow the company
needs, then all your medical checkup can be
checked from their medical shop, they can
also investigate in any hospital
and this happens whenever someone cleans a certain
amount  Insurance companies
pay a lot of money for such
investigation officers, medical
professionals. Do
subscribe, like your friends
and
you
can like me.
So, is it important to take a policy or not? From your point of view, you
declare something that there are many issues from someone,
what should I tell you, I will take an
example, if someone has a
health issue, then don't mind, if a
person has an infection, that is, his eyes are closed, then
you will be very
surprised to know that in India, nine out of 10
companies do not give policies in such cases.
Forget about it, forget about it,
Dr., this is a small town,
what is the reason behind it, it will not be difficult, it is a
matter of very big medical science, but
even in such small cases, we
fulfill the policy, it is not that all the companies do it,
but some companies do such things, then on such
small matters the company refuses to give the policy,
claim reaction, this is
our
classification, someone came to us with reference to that, then we talked to them.  I had
advised
him that he had a problem with TV many years ago while taking the policy,
I had
forgotten to tell him, now after two-three years naturally I will have to
tell the company, I started the conversation and told them about the
remedies and the company
cancelled the old policy saying
that you cannot understand the extent of this thing,
I do not say that
we are very intelligent, I have the
knowledge of the whole world, I do not talk like that,
but see, in one line it is a matter of experience,
we should always stay away from some things, so the
most important thing is which
company's policy, how much should you mix
and which feature should not be there, I say all these things are
secondary, you should always have
three things, you should always have a small
policy, if you have money then take a
big position today, second thing
if it is possible then read the terms and
conditions of the policy carefully,
download its proposal form,
read it carefully and declare everything properly, like
Rifleman Policy and
third thing, there should be a room rent limit in your policy
If you want to live in big cities, then a
single private room with AC will not suffice.
Get a deluxe room. If it is small, then a
single private home will do. You should
not fall within the limit of 1% or 2%. If
you have two-three things, that is enough. In the
last few years, there is
a very big company in India which has
allotted premium medical checkup policies till the age of 70-75 years. What happened? It will be
easy for your consultant advisor who is an intermediary in between. If you want to get
any policy done, then
secondly, many people in India do
not know about their health. Today,
if someone gets a heart attack after the Pulse Polio test,
if you do
not get your medical checkup done and do
not get it done through the company, a large part of the
company will blame you that you did
not tell them. It is important to keep this in mind that even
if the company does not get the medical checkup done, get
your health checkup done.
Every insurance professional should
talk about his profession and not about one council.
Every insurance professional has knowledge.
If the company does not get the medical checkup done, then
what harm are you doing by getting it done and
spending Rs. 24,000 in the beginning?
In the coming time, you have to make policies worth lakhs and crores in
your career, for that invest Rs. 1000-2000
initially, okay, after
paying once to your insurance agent, I will get it done only after getting the
medical checkup done. So, if you are young,
below 45 years of age, there is
no medical checkup in this company, but there are 12
companies which do not allow you to get a medical checkup done, whatever
your age may be. So,
in some companies, if you have BP and diabetes, then there is no
medical checkup, but in the last
three-four years, a lot of
importance has
started being given to our policy, that people are getting passed without medical checkup,
but if we have to take a policy, then
you should take a little care of yourself,
go there, I will give you a small
breakdown of the policy, my mother had a policy
some time ago, first of all, I have mentioned
two things in it simply, any side or
health issues,
their  In 2016, he had a small
injury on his legs and he had a small knee
surgery done.
Now after that, when we
subscribed him in the name of a minister, the company did a little more, that is, a little more, so
not only knee replacement, it was a
small operation, there is
no need to worry about it. The
company takes it so seriously even when you tell such a small thing,
whenever you do nothing,
three people are very happy in this,
first you get temporary happiness that
you will have a comfortable policy, which is intermediate
or it is a very good thing that it will be passed in the name of the channel, you will
earn two paise commission, thirdly the
company is the happiest because
tomorrow there will be any kind of dispute at home, which will
come because if it comes under do not disclose, then first
your claim will be
rejected, secondly, the company which has been
paying the policy money for so many years, that
money is not returned, the policy
is terminated, okay, and
after that, when you try to buy a policy somewhere else, then
in the proposal form it is asked whether
you have ever  Has any proposal been
rejected, has any
loading been applied, so many things are asked,
if you look carefully,
honestly, this policy buying is very
painful, it is necessary, it works very fast,
but when you do this in this way,
after that I get a
good sleep at night, work hard because
if you do not behave properly, then
when you are in that situation, you will have to work ten times harder, so
always keep one thing in
mind, I know young people,
I talk, but I get to know in
what manner,
and on top of that, I would
reduce my conversation a little, so
we would know who he is talking to, so
I am not saying that you should talk to me only, it is
not like that, if you liked this video then you can
like, you may
not like what I say, but keep this
thing in mind that you either have to
become a good client or a customer, when
you buy policies online, you
are always a customer and in many cases it is a
matter of joke, so it is
written in the name that refuse with pain  That means the chances
of getting into trouble increase. Always
try. If you live in a big city, then do
not get carried away by online marketing. If the
person who is repeatedly telling you
not to declare this, run away from there. It is
absolutely fine if your age is above 40 years and
get a policy. If there is no
company that does this, then get it done yourself. Do the declaration
properly. Take the policy from wherever you want.
You will get the policy from your 10th result
but do it in the right minute.
And if I say the same thing again, that is
how people shoot themselves in the foot. If
someone is advising you
not to declare these things
and falling into his trap, they declare
this and take an insurance policy. There are many such
people who tell us
that they took a policy from an agent, brother, with so much
information, and they changed the company,
they have stopped working. So such a
policy is called another policy, which
neither the company has any claim nor the insurance company has any claim. You have to
see that giving this cream is the
last making payment for them for the company, so never do this.
Keep thinking that there must be some company in India
which laughs when a claim comes and gives it away
without money, nobody likes it
because it is the work of the company but
many companies run on stores, so you must have received my
request, I have started a new financial venture, please
review your points,
I should say that four years ago your company cancelled the party after
informing the company about my bakery items delivered in the wrong way,
I have suffered a
loss because in the beginning I did
not take your guidance, you made a mistake
knowingly or unknowingly, but now because
life is very long, so do not do this to those
girls, by closing it,
absolutely, by
talking to some company somewhere, in this
way
our
today, if someone just wants to know that
I have done this, then
what things should I keep in mind, I will
tell them the answer to all the questions of the village, please
subscribe, thank you
very much for watching this video, thank you very much,
Vande Mataram has
happened